

CONTACT

PHONE: 0791414614

EMAIL:

Beavisser0@gmail.com/ 3626481@myuwc.ac.za

Portfolio:

https://www.clippings.me/thebumblebea

BEATRICE VISSER

Abbotsdale, Malmesbury, 7300

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Date of Birth : 16 February 1997

Marital Status:SingleSex:FemaleRace:Coloured

Nationality : South African Citizen

Health : Excellent

Language : English and Afrikaans

Criminal Record : None
Dependants : None

Driver's license : Yes – Code B

Own vehicle:YesPassport:YesWilling to relocate:yes

PROFILE

I am a graduate of the University of the Western Cape. I completed my degree in 2019. I have a BA degree in English and Political Studies. I have four years of work experience in social media management, content writing, copywriting, email campaigns, link-building articles, research, editing, and implementation of new conversion optimization tactics.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Printed Memories

Position held: Content writer

Duration: November 2022 – Currently

Contact information: +27 72 237 4301

Digi Outsource

Position held: Gambling consultant

(contract)

Duration: April 2022 – October 2022

Contact information: +27 21 528 9300

Leads Capital Group

Position held: Content writer

Duration: October 2021 – March 2022

Contact information: +27 82 676 2723

Oxford University Press

Position held: Freelance translator/editor **Duration:** April 2021 - February 2022

Contact information: +27 21 596 2485

EDUCATION

TERTIARY

• University of the Western Cape

2016 - 2019

Bachelor of Arts Degree in:

English (Major) - 2019

Modernist Literature
Contemporary Literature

*Introduction to film and media studies (Elective)

*Theatre Topics (Elective)

Political Studies (Major) - 2019

African in International Perspective Research Methodology

Electives:

*Classical culture - 2016 - 2017

*Language and communication (Linguistics) 2016 - 2018

*French - 2018

TEFL Professional Development Institute

2020

TEFL certificate 120 hours completed

SECONDARY

Swartland High School (2011 – 2015)

Highest grade passed: Grade 12 (Matric) 2015

Subjects

Tourism
Computer Applications Technology
History
Mathematical Literacy
Life Orientation
English 1st language
Afrikaans 1st Language

SKILLS

Pro efficient in 2 languages: Afrikaans and English Currently learning: Spanish – entry level

I write, edit and maintain my blog. 2016 – currently https://wordpress.com/view/bumblebeaweb.wordpress.com/

PERSONAL ATTRIBUTES

- Hard working
- Dedicated
- Ability to read a room
- People person
- Good customer service
- Telephone etiquette
- Friendly
- Ethical
- Responsible
- Fast learner
- Creative
- Trustworthy

COMPUTER LITERACY

- MS Word
- MS Excel
- MS Outlook
- MS PowerPoint
- WordPress
- Social Media
- Internet
- Web design (entry-level)